[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "What do you make of this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "It's a tough go for this guy, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Can you survive if you don't have credibility and don't have trust in the public office?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "You tell me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "CC", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "He should go, you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "Well, I don't know how you would get up and start to represent your constituents with no credibility and no trust.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "JJ", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 52, "question": "Is it the lying that has made it a completely unsurvivable scandal?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "VBG", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 53, "answer": "Neither event is pretty, particular all the photos out there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "When you go through it though, when you are the subject of headlines like this, what's it like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "It's no fun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "So, actually, honesty, when you're caught, is the best way with all these things?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", ",", "RB", ",", "NN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "Everything.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 107, "question": "Would that formula you deployed then for G.E., would that work for America as -- if you viewed it as a corporation?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "MD", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 108, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["G.E."], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 120, "question": "Or do you think the actual answer with China is to be more competitive by giving them what they need?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 121, "answer": "Out-innovating them is the way to beat China.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 167, "question": "Why aren't there more Steve Jobses being created in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "RBR", "NNP", "NNP", "VBG", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 168, "answer": "That is a great question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Steve Jobses"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 186, "question": "What are the rules?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 187, "answer": "I want to come back and ask you how we get the uncertainty out of the game.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 197, "question": "Do you share his faith, Jack?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 198, "answer": "With the right policies, certainly do.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "WP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "JJ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 216, "question": "What went so catastrophically wrong that meant that we had this terrible financial crisis?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 217, "answer": "So many things can be attributed to what caused the problem, but certainly lots of money available too easy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 219, "question": "Is that because greed kicks in?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 220, "answer": "No, I don't think it's so much greed.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 228, "question": "Who was most to blame?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "JJS", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 229, "answer": "Boy, that's a hard one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "I mean, who were the main culprits here from a business perspective?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "Well, I would have cleaned out anybody in the mortgage business who put faulty mortgages together.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "Should some of these people have gone to jail?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "I'm not -- I'm not qualified to pick that, whether that's true or not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "NNP", ":", ":", "WDT", "VBZ", "CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 263, "question": "If you'd been running Goldman Sachs, would you have allowed the multimillion dollar bonuses to be paid out after the bailout for the next few years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 264, "answer": "Look, there's a culture in Wall Street, I own (INAUDIBLE) -- which is one of the worst moments in my life.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Goldman Sachs"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 272, "question": "He said, this won't hurt my bonus, will it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ",", "DT", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 273, "answer": "All he cared about.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 290, "question": "Should they have done it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 291, "answer": "Well, I mean --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 295, "question": "So I'm not going to get drabbed into that one, OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "CD", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 296, "answer": "But it's interesting that you even hesitate, because you've been a big supporter previously, I'll grant you that, of allowing people to be paid what they should get in the marketplace.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 332, "question": "It's wrong, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 333, "answer": "Seems to be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 350, "question": "When she says something like that, does it worry you she might have her finger on the nuclear trigger within a couple years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 351, "answer": "I wouldn't support her for president.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 352, "question": "You think she'd be dangerous?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 353, "answer": "I just wouldn't support her for president.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "Why not?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "I don't think she has the gravitas or the international depth or a lot of things.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "And you think it's because of that she's getting support?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Well, I mean, people follow her.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"], "PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "RB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "JJS", "NN", ",", "NN", "NN", ":", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 365, "question": "Do you see anybody emerging on the Republican side who is the kind of ladder that you're looking for?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 366, "answer": "You know, Piers, this is a great question, because if you asked me that a month ago, I would have said, well, Mitt Romney might be best guy, et cetera -- the most obvious guy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 377, "question": "I mean, you're a Republican, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 378, "answer": "Yes, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", ":", "RB", ",", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "TO", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "But in your heart, do you think he can beat someone like Obama?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "I'm going to find out over the next 15 months -- hopefully, the next six to nine months because they're going to pick somebody in the primary.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 398, "question": "Why do you think he's doing that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 399, "answer": "He likes what he says.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 439, "question": "When you look at countries like China, India, Brazil, so on, these emerging superpowers, economic powerhouses, how should America deal with this threat, which they've never had to face before?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "IN", ",", "DT", "VBG", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "WRB", "MD", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 440, "answer": "They ought to talk about them.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China", "India", "Brazil", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "JJ", "PRP", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "PDT", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 467, "question": "What is the right way to deal with China?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 468, "answer": "Out innovate them, which we can do, which we do all the time.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 476, "question": "Do they scare you or excite you, the Chinese?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "CC", "VB", "PRP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 477, "answer": "Excite me.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 497, "question": "How do you feel about being a cute old dude, Jack?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 498, "answer": "I don't like the old part of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jack"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 540, "question": "The trick is not to let anybody see then, right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "TO", "VB", "NN", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 541, "answer": "Hide them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "That true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "Something like that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["50 dollar"]}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "Not bad, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "For a kid from Salem that went through a 50 dollar a semester college, a hell of a country, huh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 559, "question": "Does money make you happy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "NN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 560, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 570, "question": "Why isn't it recognizing that this is probably the big problem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 571, "answer": "We're manufacturing lots of great -- we don't want to manufacture t-shirts.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "What about, for example, very heavy big plant machinery and ship it to China, where they really need it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "TO", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "We are.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 576, "question": "Are we doing enough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 577, "answer": "We're doing tons of it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Isn't that where you could see real growth?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "ELCH: We're seeing it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 584, "question": "Would you like to se more companies like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 585, "answer": "Of course we do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 586, "question": "Is that one of the answers, one of the solutions?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 587, "answer": "Yes, one of the solutions is that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "Are we getting enough of this ideology at the moment in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "Yes, I think we are.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 639, "question": "What's your experience of doing business with the Chinese?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 640, "answer": "Well, it's a -- they do it their way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", ",", "CC", "MD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 665, "question": "Were you surprised by the Warren Buffett affair recently, when his top guy had to leave in what were pretty unethical circumstances?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "WP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 666, "answer": "Warren will never understand that, nor will others.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren Buffett"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 670, "question": "Were you surprised that he allowed it to happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 671, "answer": "Warren runs a very decentralized company.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Warren"]}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VB", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 676, "question": "Do you think if you'd been in his shoes and a top, top executive, running the show for you comes to you and says what that guy said to Warren Buffett, wouldn't alarm bells go off?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "CC", "VBZ", "WP", "IN", "NN", "VBD", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NNS", "VB", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 677, "answer": "They did go off for Warren.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Warren Buffett"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 694, "question": "Do you enjoy your acting?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 695, "answer": "It was my big moment in the sun, I'll tell you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 706, "question": "Best businessman in the world right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 707, "answer": "One of them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110608pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 709, "question": "Who's been to you the most inspirational over all the years, all the business people you've met?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 710, "answer": "Not one.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]